<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="6"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Your Business, Re-imagined.]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[W   h  y                                                                      F  e edbac      k
    Why
                                                                                  Feedback
    Use
       s
    U
          e
                                                                                       r
                                                                                        ati
                                                                                  Integration & Your Feedback Passport
                                                                                    t
                                                                                     eg
                                                                                                      eedback
                                                                                                    F
                                                                                                              P

                                                                                                Y
                                                                                            n &
                                                                                                  ur
                                                                                                 o
    Ideacoil?
    I deac      o il ?                                                            In e-imagine  y o our business via the  F eedback  assp o r t ® ®  r ategic mar k eting
                                                                                  R
                                                                                                                assport API. Use the API as st
                                                                                                               P
                                                                                  Re-imagine your business via the Feedback Passport API. Use the API as strategic marketing
                                                                                  and branding channels to distribute your project online, or in-person directly to your customers
                                                                                  and b r anding channels to distribute  y our p r oject online, or in-pe r son di r ectly to  y our custome r s
                         • Dri v e mo r e  r ev enue
                         • Drive more revenue
                                                                                   at
                                                                                    y
                                                                                     our business location.
                         • Capture customer trends                                 at your business location.
                                        ends
                                       r
                               e customer t
                         • Captu
                               r
                           R
                                            ed to
                                               y
                                                our business
                            eal-time analytics tailo
                         •
                                           r
                         • Real-time analytics tailored to your business
                                                                                                 s
                                                                                                d
                                                                                              a
                                                                                               r

                                                                                        t
                                                                                  Insigh
                                                                                          R
                                                                                            w
                                                                                           e
                                                                                  Insight Rewards ® ®
                                                     e
       o
   We provide knowledge and experience-based feedback on direct consumer experiences. This enables   Your business provides the reward or a free gift to facilitate the process of collecting feedback,  ,
   W
                                                      xperiences. This enables
       r
                                            ect consumer
                                           r
             wledge and
     e p
                     e
                      xperience-based
                                 f
                                  eedback on di
             o
        vide kn
                                                                                             r
                                                                                                                             r
                                                                                                                                                k
                                                                                                                    acilitate the p
                                                                                   our business p
                                                                                                                                           eedbac
                                                                                                                                           f
                                                                                  Y
                                                                                                                    f
                                                                                                     ew
                                                                                              vides the
                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                             ee gift to
                                                                                                             r
                                                                                                        r
                                                                                                                              ocess of collecting
                                                                                             o
                                                                                                        d or a f
                                                                                                       a
   companies to imp r o v e p r ofit ma r gins and inc r ease b r and l o y alt y .  and encou r age  F eedbac k e r s to contribute to  y our b r and ’ s authenticit y .  A dditionall y , Ideacoil
   companies to improve profit margins and increase brand loyalty.
                                                                                  and encourage Feedbackers to contribute to your brand’s authenticity. Additionally, Ideacoil
                                                                                   offers monetary incentives to help boost Feedbacker engagement and transparency with your
                                                                                   of
                                                                                    f
                                                                                                                                             y
                                                                                      s moneta
                                                                                            r
                                                                                            y incenti
                                                                                                                                              our
                                                                                                              eedbac
                                                                                                   es to help boost
                                                                                    e
                                                                                                              F
                                                                                                  v
                                                                                     r
                                                                                                                                 r
                                                                                                                                      ency with
                                                                                                                    er engagement and t
                                                                                                                   k
                                                                                                                                  anspa
                                                                                                                                      r
                                                                                   company.
                                                                                   compan y .
                                                                                    v
                                                                                               c
                                                                                                 i
                                                                                                t
                                                                                              a
                                                                                       &
                                                                                           t
                                                                                            e
                                                                                             r
                                                                                     e
                                                                                         In
                                                                                  Live & Interactive
                                                                                  Li
                                                                                                 v
                                                                                                  e
                                                                                  Live Reaction connects you to real-time Feedback, allowing you to reshape your marketing
                                                                                  Li v e  R eaction connects  y ou to  r eal-time  F eedbac k , all o wing  y ou to  r eshape  y our mar k eting
                                                                                  strategy and achieve results.
                                                                                  st r ate g y and achi ev e  r esults.
                                                                                                                                    uable
                                                                                                                                          I
                                                                                                                                             gh
                                                                                                                                   l
                                                                                                                                  a

                                                                                                                                 V
                                                                                                                                                s
                                                                                                                             a
                                                                                                                              i
                                                                                                                               n
                                                                                                                                          ns
                                                                                                                                                t
                                                                                                                            Gain Valuable Insights
                                                                                                                            G
                                                                                                                                             i
                                                                                                                                                o
                                                                                                                                          n
                                                                                                                                   i
                                                                                                           t
                                                                                                             in
                                                                                                    e
                                                                                                                                      xp
                                                                                                                                  h
                                                                                                                  r
                                                                                                             si
                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                                                   ghly
                                                                                                                s
                                                                                                         di
                                                                                                      i
                                                                                                       e
                                                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                       v
                                                                                                                 f
                                                                                                           c
                                                                                                     c
                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                          e
                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                                  om
                                                                                                              gh
                                                                                                                          e
                                                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                                                              n
                                                                                                                                            ed
                                                                                                                t
                                                                                                                           r
                                                                                                                                             i
                                                                                                                                         ie

                                                                                                                            s
                                                                                                                              ho a
                                                                                                                             w
                                                                                                                     F
                                                                                                                                r
                                                                                                 Y You receive direct insights from Feedbackers who are highly experienced in your
                                                                                                                                           c
                                                                                                  ou
                                                                                                                                 e
                                                                                                                     ee
                                                                                                                         c
                                                                                                                          k
                                                                                                                                        e
                                                                                                                                               y
                                                                                                                                                ur
                                                                                                                       dba
                                                                                                           y
                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                         st
                                                                                                      i
                                                                                                  p
                                                                                                 s specific industry. .
                                                                                                     c
                                                                                                    i
                                                                                                    c
                                                                                                   e
                                                                                                     f
                                                                                                       ndu
                                                                                                     i
       TODAY, THERE'S SO MUCH NOISE, SO WHAT REALLY COUNTS IS THE
       T O D A Y , THER E' S SO M U CH  N O I S E , SO WH A T  RE A L L Y  C O U NTS IS TH E
                                                L
                                                    L
                                                  HE
                                                     PS ME
                                                           T
                                                                   E
                                                                    V
                                                                     E
                                                                  I
                                                             O
                                                              A
                                                                CH
                                              OI
                           C
                         NI
                             A
                               I
                              T
            T
           LI
              Y OF
                    OMMU
                  C
                                         D
                                        I
                                          E
                                             C
                                           A
                                 N
                                O
                                  , A
                                      D
                                     N
       QUA
       QUALITY OF COMMUNICATION, AND IDEACOIL HELPS ME TO ACHIEVE
                                                                                                                           Reliable, Fast & Private
                                           TH
                                      A
                                        S
                                                            O
                                             E
                   TH
                 .
                                                           I
                                                         S
                                         K
                                                      UE
                      Y KN
                     E
                          O
                                                          T
             TH
                                 W
               A
                                   T

                                               RI
             THAT. THEY KNOW HOW TO ASK THE RIGHT QUESTIONS.    .                                                          R e l iab l e,   F a s t   &  P r i v a t e
                            W H
                                                               S
                                O
                                                             N
                T
                                                 GHT Q
                                    O
                                                                                                                               e
                                                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                           e
                                                                                                     c
                                                                                                                                 t
                                                                                                      o
                                                                                                                                      o
                                                                                                                                       s
                                                                                                                                     f

                                                                                                                                    p
                                                                                                         e
                                                                                                                                 o
                                                                                                                                        e
                                                                                                                                       t
                                                                                                          at
                                                                                                                                   hel
                                                                                                        c
                                                                                                                     ngaging d
                                                                                                                                            t am
                                                                                                                                           u
                                                                                                                                            s
                                                                                                  Idea
                                                                                                                                               o
                                                                                                                                                ng
                                                                                                       l
                                                                                                                    e
                                                                                                  Ideacoil creates an upbeat, engaging dialogue to help foster trust among
                                                                                                                                          t
                                                                                                                            alogu
                                                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                                           i
                                                                                                       i
                                                                                                            s an upbeat,
                                                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                       dba
                                                                                                                                                r
                                                                                                                                                 s
                                                                                                                                         u
                                                                                                         c

                                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                                                                           c
                                                                                                                                           us
                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                                                              ome
                                                                                                                                             t
                                                                                                                                        o
                                                                                                     F Feedbackers and your company. Through our system, your customers
                                                                                                                  r
                                                                                                            r
                                                                                                                       an
                                                                                                                  u
                                                                                                                         . Th
                                                                                                                            ough our
                                                                                                                    o
                                                                                                                           r
                                                                                                                     m
                                                                                                                      p
                                                                                                                    c
                                                                                                            s and
                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                                                 o
                                                                                                                                   y
                                                                                                                y
                                                                                                                                   stem,
                                                                                                                                  s
                                                                                                          k
                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                           e
         OUTREACH MUSIC FESTIVAL & ACADEMY, SCHWAZ, AUSTRIA
         OUTR E A CH M U SIC  F E S TI V AL  &   A C ADEM Y , SCH W AZ, AU S TR I A                    p provide faster, higher quality reviews that only you have access to. .
                                                                                                                        t
                                                                                                                                             e
                                                                                                            as
                                                                                                                       i
                                                                                                               r
                                                                                                       r
                                                                                                                                                o
                                                                                                               , higher qual
                                                                                                                                              s
                                                                                                              t
                                                                                                              e
                                                                                                                                               s t
                                                                                                                                        a
                                                                                                                                  o
                                                                                                         v
                                                                                                                             w
                                                                                                                              s that
                                                                                                          de
                                                                                                                                     y
                                                                                                                                      o
                                                                                                                                   nly
                                                                                                                                      u h
                                                                                                         i
                                                                                                            f

                                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                                                                            cc
                                                                                                        o
                                                                                                                          e
                                                                                                                                          e a
                                                                                                                                         v
                                                                                                                            e
                                                                                                                           v
                                                                                                                           i]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[W h y  F e edbac      k
 Why
       Feedback
 Use
 s
 U
 e
            r
             ati
       Integration & Your Feedback Passport
         t
          eg
                          eedback
                         F
                                  P

                    Y
                 n &
                      ur
                     o
 Ideacoil?
 I deac o il ?  In e-imagine  y o our business via the  F eedback  assp o r t ® ®  r ategic mar k eting
       R
                                     assport API. Use the API as st
                                    P
       Re-imagine your business via the Feedback Passport API. Use the API as strategic marketing
       and branding channels to distribute your project online, or in-person directly to your customers
       and b r anding channels to distribute  y our p r oject online, or in-pe r son di r ectly to  y our custome r s
 • Dri v e mo r e  r ev enue
 • Drive more revenue
       at
         y
         our business location.
 • Capture customer trends  at your business location.
 ends
 r
 e customer t
 • Captu
 r
 R
 ed to
 y
 our business
 eal-time analytics tailo
 •
 r
 • Real-time analytics tailored to your business
                     s
                    d
                  a
                   r

             t
       Insigh
              R
                 w
                e
       Insight Rewards ® ®
 e
 o
 We provide knowledge and experience-based feedback on direct consumer experiences. This enables   Your business provides the reward or a free gift to facilitate the process of collecting feedback,  ,
 W
 xperiences. This enables
 r
 ect consumer
 r
 wledge and
 e p
 e
 xperience-based
 f
 eedback on di
 o
 vide kn
                 r
                                                  r
                                                                    k
                                         acilitate the p
        our business p
                                                                eedbac
                                                               f
       Y
                                        f
                         ew
                  vides the
                         r
                                  ee gift to
                                 r
                            r
                                                  ocess of collecting
                  o
                            d or a f
                           a
 companies to imp r o v e p r ofit ma r gins and inc r ease b r and l o y alt y .  and encou r age  F eedbac k e r s to contribute to  y our b r and ’ s authenticit y .  A dditionall y , Ideacoil
 companies to improve profit margins and increase brand loyalty.
       and encourage Feedbackers to contribute to your brand’s authenticity. Additionally, Ideacoil
       offers monetary incentives to help boost Feedbacker engagement and transparency with your
       of
        f
                                                                 y
          s moneta
                r
                 y incenti
                                                                  our
                                   eedbac
                       es to help boost
         e
                                  F
                      v
         r
                                                      r
                                                           ency with
                                        er engagement and t
                                       k
                                                      anspa
                                                          r
       company.
       compan y .
         v
                   c
                     i
                    t
                  a
           &
               t
                e
                 r
          e
              In
       Live & Interactive
       Li
                      v
                       e
       Live Reaction connects you to real-time Feedback, allowing you to reshape your marketing
       Li v e  R eaction connects  y ou to  r eal-time  F eedbac k , all o wing  y ou to  r eshape  y our mar k eting
       strategy and achieve results.
       st r ate g y and achi ev e  r esults.
                                                        uable
                                                              I
                                                                  gh
                                                       l
                                                      a

                                                     V
                                                                     s
                                                  a
                                                   i
                                                   n
                                                               ns
                                                                    t
                                                Gain Valuable Insights
                                                G
                                                                 i
                                                                    o
                                                               n
                                                       i
                                t
                                 in
                         e
                                                           xp
                                                       h
                                      r
                                  si
                        r
                                                       ghly
                                     s
                             di
                           i
                            e
                                                          e
                           v
                                      f
                               c
                         c
                              r
                              e
                          e
                                       om
                                   gh
                                               e
                                                             r
                                                                  n
                                                                ed
                                    t
                                                r
                                                                  i
                                                             ie

                                                s
                                                  ho a
                                                 w
                                         F
                                                     r
                      Y You receive direct insights from Feedbackers who are highly experienced in your
                                                               c
                      ou
                                                     e
                                          ee
                                             c
                                              k
                                                            e
                                                                   y
                                                                     ur
                                           dba
                               y
                               r
                             st
                           i
                      p
                      s specific industry. .
                          c
                         i
                        c
                       e
                         f
                           ndu
                         i
 TODAY, THERE'S SO MUCH NOISE, SO WHAT REALLY COUNTS IS THE
 T O D A Y , THER E' S SO M U CH  N O I S E , SO WH A T  RE A L L Y  C O U NTS IS TH E
 L
 L
  HE
 PS ME
 T
 E
 V
 E
 I
 O
 A
 CH
 OI
 C
 NI
 A
 I
 T
 T
 LI
 Y OF
 OMMU
 C
 D
 I
 E
 C
 A
 N
 O
 , A
 D
 N
 QUA
 QUALITY OF COMMUNICATION, AND IDEACOIL HELPS ME TO ACHIEVE
                                               Reliable, Fast & Private
  TH
 A
 S
 O
 E
  TH
 .
 I
 S
 K
 UE
 Y KN
 E
 O
 T
 TH
 W
 A
 T

 RI
 THAT. THEY KNOW HOW TO ASK THE RIGHT QUESTIONS. .  R e l iab l e,   F a s t   &  P r i v a t e
 W H
 S
 O
 N
 T
 GHT Q
 O
                                                    e
                                                             r
                             r
                                e
                         c
                                                      t
                          o
                                                          o
                                                           s
                                                          f

                                                         p
                              e
                                                     o
                                                            e
                                                            t
                              at
                                                       hel
                            c
                                         ngaging d
                                                                 t am
                                                               u
                                                                s
                       Idea
                                                                    o
                                                                    ng
                           l
                                         e
                       Ideacoil creates an upbeat, engaging dialogue to help foster trust among
                                                               t
                                                alogu
                                                               r
                                                i
                           i
                                s an upbeat,
                                                              r
                           dba
                                                                     r
                                                                     s
                                                             u
                              c

                                                            y
                                                               c
                                                                us
                           e
                                                                  ome
                                                                 t
                                                             o
                         F Feedbackers and your company. Through our system, your customers
                                       r
                                r
                                           an
                                      u
                                             . Th
                                                ough our
                                        o
                                                r
                                         m
                                          p
                                        c
                                 s and
                                             y
                                     o
                                                       y
                                     y
                                                        stem,
                                                      s
                               k
                          e
                               e
 OUTREACH MUSIC FESTIVAL & ACADEMY, SCHWAZ, AUSTRIA
 OUTR E A CH M U SIC  F E S TI V AL  &   A C ADEM Y , SCH W AZ, AU S TR I A  p provide faster, higher quality reviews that only you have access to. .
                                            t
                                                                  e
                                 as
                                            i
                                   r
                            r
                                                                     o
                                    , higher qual
                                                                  s
                                  t
                                   e
                                                                   s t
                                                             a
                                                      o
                             v
                                                 w
                                                  s that
                              de
                                                         y
                                                          o
                                                       nly
                                                           u h
                              i
                                f

                                              r
                                             y
                                                                cc
                            o
                                              e
                                                              e a
                                                              v
                                                e
                                               v
                                                i]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[ADDRESSI
                                                                                                               E
                                                                                                                 ELEPHANTS IN TH
                                                                                ADDRESSING THE ELEPHANTS IN THE ROOMOOM
                                                                                                                                             E
                                                                                                       G TH
                                                                                                     N
                                                                                                                                                R

       I FEEL FEEDBACK TO BUSINESSES IS WONDERFUL, ESPECIALLY AS A
                                                                                                                            e
                                                                                                                       s and
                                                                                                                            r
                                                                                                                                s a
                                                                                                                                  r
                                                                                                                             vi
                                                                                                                              ew
                                                                                                e
                                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                  ou finding that generic su
                                                                                                 y
                                                                                               r
                                                                                              A
                                                                                                                      y
                                                                                                                     v
                                                                                                                      e
       LOCAL PERSON IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD, BECAUSE IT KEEPS A GREAT                        Are you finding that generic surveys and reviews are no longer adding any real e no longer adding any real
                                                                                                               f
                                                                                                     our customer
                                                                                                    y
                                                                                              v
                                                                                               alue to
                                                                                                                eedback p
        RELATIONSHIP WHEN PEOPLE ARE GOOD TO YOU. WHAT MORE CAN                          value to your customer feedback process?rocess?
                                                                                                              f
                                                                                                                             y
                                                                                                                                      y
                                                                                                                              ou to
                                                                                                                           w
                                                                                                                          o
                                                                                                              eedback that all
                                                                                           w important is actionable
                                                                                                                            s
                                                                                          o
                                                                                                                                  ocus
                                                                                                                                  f
                                                                                         H
           HAPPEN, BUT BETTER BUSINESS AND CUSTOMER SERVICE?                        How important is actionable feedback that allows you to focus your marketing our marketing
                                                                                                     ofit dri
                                                                                                          v
                                                                                                              or
                                                                                                  y p
                                                                                                           e
                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                           r
                                                                                                                y
                                                                                                  e
                                                                                                 k
                                                                                                            s
                                                                                         activity on
                                                                                                             f
                                                                                    activity on key profit drivers for your business?our business?
                                                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                  y
                                                                                                                f
                                                                                                 e
                                                                                                                eedback that is
                                                                                                                                          ed to
                                                                                                                                              y
                                                                                              H
                                                                                               av
                                                                                                   ou g
                                                                                                           r
                                                                                                                           n
                                                                                                       wn ti
                                                                                                       o
                                                                                                      r
                                                                                                           ed of
                                                                                                                            ’t completely tailo
                      CATHEDRAL WINE, NEW YORK, NY                                       Have you grown tired of feedback that isn’t completely tailored to your unique our unique
                                                                                                               esult, brings no clarity to
                                                                                         requirements and as a result, brings no clarity to your business?our business?
                                                                                                  r
                                                                                               equi
                                                                                                               r
                                                                                                                                  y
                                                                                              r
                                                                                                  ements and as a
    How                                                                             What type of an impact would real-time feedback from potential customers who ers who
                                                                                                       a
                                                                                                 f an im
                                                                                                                 t
                                                                                                       ct
                                                                                                              e
                                                                                                               al-
                                                                                                          ould
                                                                                                      p
                                                                                                         w

                                                                                                              r
                                                                                                                  im
                                                                                             ype
                                                                                                                         c
                                                                                                                               pote
                                                                                                                                  n
                                                                                                                                   ti
                                                                                         What
                                                                                                                       dba
                                                                                                                                       sto
                                                                                                                            o
                                                                                                                                      u
                                                                                                                            r
                                                                                                                          k f
                                                                                             t
                                                                                                                             m
                                                                                                                                    al
                                                                                                                   e

                                                                                                                     f
                                                                                                                                         m
                                                                                                                                      c
                                                                                                                     ee
                                                                                                o
    To                                                                              are genuinely interested in your product or service offering have on your business?siness?
                                                                                                          i
                                                                                                                             f
                                                                                                            our
                                                                                                                                     o

                                                                                                                                      n
                                                                                                          n
                                                                                                                                  a
                                                                                                                                   v
                                                                                                                                    e
                                                                                                                              er
                                                                                                           y
                                                                                                                               ing h
                                                                                                                     or
                                                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                                r
                                                                                                                                         u

                                                                                                                    t
                                                                                                                   c
                                                                                                                 du
                                                                                                                o
                                                                                                                                           bu
                                                                                                                      se

                                                                                                                          e
                                                                                                                                       y
                                                                                                                             f
                                                                                                                            o
                                                                                                                        r
                                                                                                                                        o
                                                                                                                         vi
                                                                                                                          c
                                                                                                               p
                                                                                         r
                                                                                                     r
                                                                                         a
                                                                                                        ed
                                                                                                      est
                                                                                          e g
                                                                                               i
                                                                                               nely in
                                                                                             nu
                                                                                                    te
                                                                                            e
                                                                                                         S
                                                                                               OIL AN
                                                                                                           WE
                                                                                            C
                                                                                          A
                                                                                     IDE
                                                                                                                             C
                                                                                                                R
                                                                                                                   S THE
    Use                                                                         IDEACOIL ANSWERS THE CALLALL                              r e to c r
                                                                                                       r
                                                                                     Ideacoil is a business pe
                                                                                                          ’
                                                                                                          s solution to all of these challenges and mo
                                                                                                         n
                                                                                                       so
                                                                                Ideacoil is a business person’s solution to all of these challenges and more to create new eate new
    Ideacoil                                                                    opportunities for business growth. As a trusted authority in feedback, we achieve this by:e this by:
                                                                                                                                 eedbac
                                                                                                         r
                                                                                               f
                                                                                                or business g
                                                                                                                                f
                                                                                                                                      k
                                                                                                           wth. As a trusted authority in
                                                                                                                                       , we achi
                                                                                                                                             ev
                                                                                                          o
                                                                                     opportunities
                                                                                                  y
                                                                                                                     viding
                                                                                                                         e
                                                                                                                                        our bu
                                                                                                       get audience and p
                                                                                                                                             er
                                                                                                                   r
                                                                                                                    o
                                                                                                                                            y
                                                                                                                              e insight into
                                                                                                   our ta
                                                                                                                                                r
                                                                                                                              v
                                                                                          Identifying
                                                                                                                                               pe
                                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                     Identifying your target audience and providing extensive insight into your buyer personas so sonas so
                                                                                                      r
                                                                                                                          xtensi
                                                                                              ou tho
                                                                                              y
                                                                                          that
                        01                Start Re-Imagine                           that you thoroughly understand your ideal customer.our ideal customer.  f eedback with incenti v es, and
                                                                                                  r
                                                                                                   oughly unde
                                                                                                                y
                                                                                                           r
                                                                                                           stand
                                          Design your interactive feedback
                                                                                          P
                                                                                                              ocess to solicit customer
                                                                                                              r
                                                                                     Providing a unique tool and process to solicit customer feedback with incentives, and help you help you
                                                                                            o
                                                                                             viding a unique tool and p
                                                                                           r
                                          questionnaire. Offer a  custom reward to the
                                                                                                                     e
                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                                      v
                                                                                          optimize
                                                                                                                    e
                                                                                                 our p
                                                                                                            vices, or li
                                                                                                y
                                                                                                     oducts, se
                                                                                                            r
                                                                                                                   v
                                          Feedbackers in exchange for their insights.  optimize your products, services, or live event spectacles.ent spectacles.  y our
                                                                                                                      ou can consistently implement into
                                                                                     Delivering real-time actionable data that you can consistently implement into your business to business to
                                                                                                  eal-time actionable data that
                                                                                              ering
                                                                                          Deli
                                                                                                 r
                                                                                                                      y
                                                                                             v
                                                                                             act mo
                                                                                     attract more high-quality prospects that you can convert into customers.ert into customers.
                                                                                          att
                                                                                                            r
                                                                                                                             v
                                                                                            r
                                                                                                             ospects that
                                                                                                                     y
                                                                                                                      ou can con
                                                                                                  e high-quality p
                                                                                                 r
                                                                                              aging the full p
                                                                                                        o
                                                                                          L
                                                                                                                     eedback to help
                                                                                           ev
                                                                                                                                y
                                                                                     Leveraging the full power of purposeful feedback to help you meet crucial short-term goals ou meet crucial short-term goals
                                                                                             e
                                                                                                                     f
                                                                                             r
                                                                                                         wer of purposeful
                 02            Invite The Crowd                                      and propel your business towards long-term sustainable success.ds long-term sustainable success.
                                                                                                  y
                                                                                                            o
                                                                                               opel
                                                                                                              a
                                                                                                               r
                                                                                                             w
                                                                                          and p
                                                                                              r
                                                                                                   our business t
                               Invite current customers and industry Feedbackers to
                               participate in your online or in-person events.
                                                                                                                                            C
                                                                                                                                           U
                                                                                        I
                                                                                                L A
                                                                                                         S ME
                                                                                                                                   C
                                                                                                       W
                                                                                                                   AIN
                                                                                                                                       S
                                                                                                      O
                                                                                                                                        T
                                                                                                                  G
                                                                                                                                    ON
                                                                                                                                         R
                                                                                   IDEACOIL ALLOWS ME TO GAIN ACCESS TO CONSTRUCTIVE AND TIVE AND
                                                                                               I
                                                                                             C
                                                                                                              T
                                                                                                                          CESS
                                                                                                                                T
                                                                                                                       A
                                                                                                                O
                                                                                          E
                                                                                           A
                                                                                                                                 O
                                                                                              O
                                                                                         D
                                                                                                                        C
                                                                                                    L
                                                                                                   L
                                                                                            R
                                                                                          E
                                                                                                N
                                                                                             SO
                                                                                                                         O
                                                                                                         NS
                                                                                                         I
                                                                                                                                         I
                                                                                                  LI
                                                                                                                          THE
                                                                                                 A
                                                                                                                                    F
                                                                                                    ZED
                                                                                                                                      ESS
                                                                                                            I
                                                                                                                                  R
                                                                                         P
                                                                                                                                   O
                                                                                                             GHTS F
                                                                                                                                 P
                                                                                                                              R
                                                                                                                    R
                                                                                    PERSONALIZED INSIGHTS FROM OTHER PROFESSIONALS AND ONALS AND
                                                                                                                     OM
          03             Understand Your Customer And Ratings                                              THIS IS BIG!S BIG!
                                                                                                                      I
                                                                                                                   I
                                                                                                                TH
                                                                                                                    S
                         Manage feedback from your personal dashboard. Analyze the data
                         to find patterns and quickly determine what work needs to be
                         recalibrated.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[ADDRESSI
                                   E
                                      ELEPHANTS IN TH
    ADDRESSING THE ELEPHANTS IN THE ROOMOOM
                                                                  E
                            G TH
                         N
                                                                     R

 I FEEL FEEDBACK TO BUSINESSES IS WONDERFUL, ESPECIALLY AS A
                                                 e
                                            s and
                                                r
                                                     s a
                                                       r
                                                 vi
                                                   ew
                    e
                                         r
                      ou finding that generic su
                     y
                   r
                   A
                                           y
                                         v
                                          e
 LOCAL PERSON IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD, BECAUSE IT KEEPS A GREAT   Are you finding that generic surveys and reviews are no longer adding any real e no longer adding any real
                                    f
                          our customer
                         y
                   v
                   alue to
                                    eedback p
 RELATIONSHIP WHEN PEOPLE ARE GOOD TO YOU. WHAT MORE CAN   value to your customer feedback process?rocess?
                                  f
                                                 y
                                                           y
                                                  ou to
                                               w
                                              o
                                  eedback that all
               w important is actionable
                                                s
              o
                                                       ocus
                                                      f
             H
 HAPPEN, BUT BETTER BUSINESS AND CUSTOMER SERVICE?  How important is actionable feedback that allows you to focus your marketing our marketing
                         ofit dri
                              v
                                  or
                       y p
                               e
                         r
                                r
                                    y
                      e
                     k
                                s
             activity on
                                  f
        activity on key profit drivers for your business?our business?
                                                              r
                      y
                                    f
                     e
                                    eedback that is
                                                              ed to
                                                                  y
                   H
                    av
                       ou g
                               r
                                                n
                            wn ti
                           o
                          r
                                ed of
                                                ’t completely tailo
 CATHEDRAL WINE, NEW YORK, NY  Have you grown tired of feedback that isn’t completely tailored to your unique our unique
                                    esult, brings no clarity to
              requirements and as a result, brings no clarity to your business?our business?
                      r
                   equi
                                   r
                                                      y
                   r
                       ements and as a
 How    What type of an impact would real-time feedback from potential customers who ers who
                           a
                     f an im
                                     t
                            ct
                                   e
                                   al-
                               ould
                          p
                              w

                                  r
                                      im
                  ype
                                              c
                                                   pote
                                                      n
                                                       ti
             What
                                           dba
                                                            sto
                                                 o
                                                           u
                                                r
                                              k f
                 t
                                                  m
                                                        al
                                        e

                                         f
                                                              m
                                                          c
                                          ee
                    o
 To     are genuinely interested in your product or service offering have on your business?siness?
                              i
                                                 f
                                 our
                                                          o

                                                          n
                               n
                                                       a
                                                        v
                                                        e
                                                  er
                                y
                                                   ing h
                                         or
                                                              r
                                    r
                                                             u

                                        t
                                       c
                                     du
                                     o
                                                                bu
                                           se

                                               e
                                                            y
                                                 f
                                                o
                                            r
                                                            o
                                             vi
                                              c
                                   p
              r
                         r
             a
                            ed
                          est
              e g
                   i
                   nely in
                 nu
                        te
                e
                              S
                   OIL AN
                                WE
                 C
               A
         IDE
                                                 C
                                     R
                                       S THE
 Use  IDEACOIL ANSWERS THE CALLALL                            r e to c r
                           r
         Ideacoil is a business pe
                              ’
                              s solution to all of these challenges and mo
                             n
                            so
    Ideacoil is a business person’s solution to all of these challenges and more to create new eate new
 Ideacoil  opportunities for business growth. As a trusted authority in feedback, we achieve this by:e this by:
                                                     eedbac
                              r
                   f
                    or business g
                                                    f
                                                          k
                               wth. As a trusted authority in
                                                           , we achi
                                                                 ev
                              o
         opportunities
                      y
                                         viding
                                             e
                                                             our bu
                           get audience and p
                                                                  er
                                        r
                                        o
                                                                 y
                                                   e insight into
                       our ta
                                                                     r
                                                  v
               Identifying
                                                                   pe
                                                            y
          Identifying your target audience and providing extensive insight into your buyer personas so sonas so
                           r
                                              xtensi
                   ou tho
                  y
               that
 01  Start Re-Imagine  that you thoroughly understand your ideal customer.our ideal customer.  f eedback with incenti v es, and
                       r
                       oughly unde
                                    y
                               r
                                stand
 Design your interactive feedback
               P
                                   ocess to solicit customer
                                  r
          Providing a unique tool and process to solicit customer feedback with incentives, and help you help you
                o
                 viding a unique tool and p
                r
 questionnaire. Offer a  custom reward to the
                                         e
                         r
                                          v
               optimize
                                        e
                     our p
                                 vices, or li
                     y
                         oducts, se
                                r
                                        v
 Feedbackers in exchange for their insights.  optimize your products, services, or live event spectacles.ent spectacles.  y our
                                           ou can consistently implement into
          Delivering real-time actionable data that you can consistently implement into your business to business to
                      eal-time actionable data that
                  ering
               Deli
                      r
                                          y
                 v
                 act mo
          attract more high-quality prospects that you can convert into customers.ert into customers.
               att
                                 r
                                                  v
                 r
                                 ospects that
                                          y
                                           ou can con
                      e high-quality p
                      r
                  aging the full p
                            o
               L
                                          eedback to help
                ev
                                                     y
          Leveraging the full power of purposeful feedback to help you meet crucial short-term goals ou meet crucial short-term goals
                 e
                                         f
                  r
                             wer of purposeful
 02  Invite The Crowd  and propel your business towards long-term sustainable success.ds long-term sustainable success.
                      y
                                o
                   opel
                                  a
                                   r
                                 w
               and p
                  r
                       our business t
 Invite current customers and industry Feedbackers to
 participate in your online or in-person events.
                                                                C
                                                               U
            I
                    L A
                             S ME
                                                       C
                           W
                                       AIN
                                                           S
                          O
                                                             T
                                      G
                                                        ON
                                                              R
       IDEACOIL ALLOWS ME TO GAIN ACCESS TO CONSTRUCTIVE AND TIVE AND
                    I
                 C
                                   T
                                              CESS
                                                    T
                                            A
                                    O
              E
                A
                                                     O
                  O
             D
                                             C
                         L
                        L
                R
               E
                    N
                 SO
                                              O
                              NS
                             I
                                                              I
                       LI
                                               THE
                     A
                                                         F
                         ZED
                                                          ESS
                                 I
                                                      R
             P
                                                       O
                                 GHTS F
                                                     P
                                                   R
                                        R
        PERSONALIZED INSIGHTS FROM OTHER PROFESSIONALS AND ONALS AND
                                          OM
 03  Understand Your Customer And Ratings  THIS IS BIG!S BIG!
                                           I
                                       I
                                    TH
                                        S
 Manage feedback from your personal dashboard. Analyze the data
 to find patterns and quickly determine what work needs to be
 recalibrated.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[e
                         id
                    ideacoilacoil                   ®
                                               ®
                  I
                                  s.
                                                          w
           al
                                                       e
                    nsight
                                           e
                                        R
                                              al
                                                    R

                                                             a
      R
                                                                r
 R e al  I nsight s.   R e al  R e w a r ds .ds .
         e
                        E

                          P
                                                  R
                   E
                  G
                                                   S
                      TH
                           O
                                       E
                                        E
                                      F
                                    F

                                         D
                             WER O
     LEVERAGE THE POWER OF FEEDBACKERS  TO ENHANCE O ENHANCE
                                              CKE
                                           B
                                            A
          L
            V
           E
                                                       T
                 A
               R

              E
                                                     ®
                                                ®
                         ERIE
            S
                                CES A
               OME
                                              E B
             T
                                             V
    CUSTOMER EXPERIENCES AND DRIVE BUSINESS GROWTHWTH
                                                       ESS G
                                                              O
                              N
                        P
                                                             R
                                      N
                      EX
                                                     N
                   R
           U
                                       D DRI
                                                   SI
         C
                                                  U
  Highly targeted marketing has never been more critical to business success than it is today.  is today.
             r
                                           c
                                                          e
                                       r
                                            al
                               er been mo
                                                                 t
                                          i
                                          ti
                                                           ss than i
                                       e cr
                             ev
               t
                                                     s
                     k
                                                  s
       Highly ta
                                                    s
                                                  ine
                     eting has n
                ed ma
                                               o bu
                                                       ucc
             ge
                                              t
                    r
                                                      s
                                      o
                                                     y
                                                      ou
                                                u
                                           help
                                                        r
                                              y
                                               o
                                                         business obj
                                       n t
                                         o
                                                 r
                                                 each
                               s in
                     y
                      ou
                 u
                  t
                    at
                         f
                         i
                         nger ti
                                  ormati
                       r
                                 f
  Ideacoil will put at your finger tips information to help you reach your business objectives.ectives.
           o
         e
         a
          c
       Id
            i
               ll
                              p
                p
            l w
              i
                            n
                           i
                                              o
                                            si
                                           i
                             or
                             f
                                             t
                          e
                      r
                                                   b
                     o
               For more information, please visit our website at: site at:
                    F
                         r
                                               ur
                                                 we
                        m
                        o
                                 tio
                                        as
                                         e
                                       e
                                   n,
                                     p
                                      l
                               ma

                                           v
                                  w
                          www.ideacoil.comil.com
                                      e
                                         o
                                    id
                                       ac
                                   .
                               ww
                                         di
                                 n
                                       s
                              or
                                  t
                                    c
                                     t u
                                c
                                          r
                                o
                         or contact us directly at:ectly at:
                                   a
                              h
                               o
                                         -
                                 e
                             P
                                n
                                  : +1-646
                        Phone: +1-646-752-0430752-0430
                       Email: team@ideacoil.comil.com
                                    m
                                   a
                             mail: t
                            E
                                        ideac
                                            o
                                      @
                                  e
                                  F
                                   e
                             Feature:ature:
 © 2021 Ideacoil LLC. P-1002-5C. P-1002-5
              L
     © 2021 Ideacoil L]]></page></pages></Search>